I’m on a mission
Don’t need permission
No matter what I’m gonna make my own decisions
I’m talking you
You want it too
I’m pretty and kind, but watch how I turn into Monster
예쁘고 착한 내가 어떻게 변할지 monster
Remember Me
Sting like a bee
Personality like a starving lion
굶주린 사자 같은 personality
네 맘 빼고 다른 것은 원하지 않아
I don’t want anything but your heart
I would never do you wrong
You’ll regret it when I’m gone
You
Slightly harder
좀 더 강하게
Even faster
더 빠르게
Gonna swing away
날려 버릴게
You
Got a lot to say
What a big mistake
Batter Batter Batter Up
Batter Up Batter Up Batter Up
Yeah
Hit it I run
Hit it 난 달려
Never can stop
Rappin Start
Rappin 시작
Shot in your ears
네 귀에 shot
Screams will turn into cheers loud
비명은 함성이 될 거야 loud
Surprise
서프라이즈
Yo The rise of the monster
Yo 몬스터의 등장
My way will be shining forever way
내가 가는 길이 기리 빛이 나리 way
Square up, I’m going going gone (gone)
어깨 펴고 난 Going going gone (gone)
Took over the baton, and all set
바통 받고 준비 완료
Quickly Run Run Run Run
후다닥 Run Run Run Run
Who can stop me I step on it harder Just get out of my way
누가 날 막아 난 더 세게 밟아 너네가 좀 알아서 비켜
I don’t pretend to be innocent You want me? but look in the mirror
순진한 척 나는 그딴 거 안 해 날 원해? but look in the mirror
Never get tired volume up, light em up
지치지 않아 계속 volume up, light em up
Burn the stage Take everything away homerun
무대 위를 태워 싹 다 치워버려 homerun
Like a Boss Baby Imma Boss Baby
Rip it up everything like brrra
모두 다 찢어 Iike brrra
Remember Me
Sting like a bee
We are the MVP rocking the stage
무대를 갖고 노는 우린 MVP
I don’t want anything but your heart
네 맘 빼고 다른 것은 원하지 않아
I would never do you wrong
You’ll regret it when I’m gone
You
Slightly harder
좀 더 강하게
Even faster
더 빠르게
Gonna swing away
날려 버릴게
You
Got a lot to say
What a big mistake
Batter Batter Batter Up
Batter Up Batter Up Batter Up
So listen up, everybody
Volume up Move on
소릴 높여 Move on
We are the Monsters of the world
Batter up Right now
Batter up 지금 당장
Let’s run anywhere
뛰어보자 어디든
Let me show you who we are
(Batter up up up up)
Everybody
Volume up Move on
소릴 높여 Move on
We are the Monsters of the world
Batter up Right now
Batter up 지금 당장
Let’s run anywhere
뛰어보자 어디든
Let me show you who we are
(Batter Batter Batter up)